wopular.com 2018-05-12

# Privacy Policy | WOPULAR

**Information Collection and Use by Wopular**

Wopular logs non-personally-identifiable information including IP address and browser type, from users and visitors to the site. This data is used to manage the website, track usage and improve the website services. This non-personally-identifiable information may be shared with third-parties to provide more relevant services and advertisements to members. User IP addresses are recorded for security and monitoring purposes.

**Use of Cookies**

Wopular uses cookies to record session information, for purposes including ensuring that visitors are not repeatedly offered the same advertisements, advertising, and Web page content based on browser type. You may be able to configure your browser to accept or reject all or some cookies, or notify you when a cookie is set -- each browser is different, so check the "Help" menu of your browser to learn how to change your cookie preferences. Please note that Wopular allows 3rd party advertisers that are presenting advertisements on some of our pages to set and access their cookies on your computer. Advertisers' use of cookies is subject to their own privacy policies, not the Wopular Privacy Policy.

**Links**

Wopular contains links to sites. Wopular is not responsible for the privacy policies and/or practices on other sites. Our privacy policy only governs information collected on Wopular.

**Third Party Advertising**

Ads appearing on this Web site may be delivered to users by Wopular or one of our Web advertising partners. Our Web advertising partners may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement. In this way, ad servers may compile information about where you, or others who are using your computer, saw their advertisements and determine which ads are clicked on. This information allows an ad network to deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This privacy statement covers the use of cookies by Wopular and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

**Changes in Our Privacy Policy**

From time to time we may make changes to our privacy policy. If we make changes, we will post them on our site to make users aware of what the changes are so users will always be aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and when we may disclose it. A User is bound by any minor changes to the policy when she or he uses the site after those changes have been posted. If, however, we are going to use users' personally identifiable information in a manner materially different from that stated at the time of collection we will notify by posting a notice on our Web site for 30 days.

**Contacting the Web Site**

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, please [contact us](http://www.wopular.com/contact).
